fooddemocracynow.org 2014-05-19

# Food Democracy Now

**How personal information is collected, used, and shared**

We do not share the information you've given us with unaffiliated groups without your explicit permission. For petitions, letters to the editor, and surveys you've signed or completed, we treat your name, city, state, and comments as public information. We will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities.

We will not make your street address publicly available, but we may transmit it to members of Congress, the President, or other targets specifically noted on the signup page. We will also use your first name to indicate the latest actions taken on our site, which you can [view here](http://www.fooddemocracynow.org/campaigns/).

 **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

Food Democracy Now has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

We will send you updates on this and other important campaigns by email. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from our email list, you may do so. 

If you would like to unsubscribe from receiving messages, please [click here](http://action.fooddemocracynow.org/cms/unsubscribe/unsubscribe/).

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Food Democracy Now  

 _This document was last updated on March 7, 2013_
